Guide to the Willard Straight Hall records, 1925-2004.
Willard Straight Hall records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Willard Straight Hall records, 1925-2004.
35-7-503
Willard Straight Hall (Ithaca, N.Y.)
43.5 cubic ft.
Correspondence, financial records, printed material
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files of Cornell University's student union include files relating to the creation of the student union, correspondence, financial records, printed material, scrapbooks, guestbooks, and some Straight family correspondence.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files of Cornell University's student union include files relating to the creation of the student union, correspondence, financial records, printed material, scrapbooks, guest books, and some Straight family correspondence. Also some files regarding the Psi Upsilon fraternity.
Includes a copy of The Journal of the Royal Architectural Institute of Canada, University of Toronto Number, Vol. 2, January-February 1925, No. 1 with photographs of Hart House at the University of Toronto, one of the inspirations for Willard Straight Hall.
Photos of Christmas events and decorations in the Straight ca. 1955.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Willard Straight Hall (Ithaca, N.Y.); Straight family.; Cornell University--Students.; Psi Upsilon Fraternity--Chi Chapter (Cornell University)
Subjects:
Student unions--New York (State)--Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Willard Straight Records
Box 1-2
Series II. Psi Upsilon Records
Box 2
Series III. Committee and Building Reports
Box 2-6
Series IV. Payroll Reports
Box 27
Series V. Drama, Theater and WSH
Box 27
Series VI. Board of Governors Meeting Reports
Box 22
Series VII. House Administration
Box 27-28
Series VIII. Willard Straight Hall Activities
Box 30
Series IX. Alphabetical Subject Files 1925-27
Box 6-7
Series X. Alphabetical Subject Files 1927
Box 7, 30
Series XI. Alphabetical Subject Files 1928
Box 7-8
Series XII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1929
Box 9
Series XIII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1930
Box 9-11
Series XIV. Alphabetical Subject Files 1931
Box 11-12
Series XV. Alphabetical Subject Files 1932
Box 12-13
Series XVI. Alphabetical Subject Files 1933-1935
Box 13-17
Series XVII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1936
Box 17-19
Series XVIII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1937
Box 19-20
Series XIX. Alphabetical Subject Files 1938
Box 20-21
Series XX. Alphabetical Subject Files 1939-40
Box 22-25
Subseries University Unions, 1939
Box 24-25
Series XXI. Alphabetical Subject Files 1940-41
Box 25-26, 29-29
Series XXII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1941-42
Box 26-27, 30
Series XXIII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1943-44
Box 31
Series XXIV. Alphabetical Subject Files 1946-47
Box 31
Series XXV. Willard Straight Correspondence 1940's and 50's
Box 31-32
Series XXVI. Financial Data 1925-44
Box 33
Series XXVII. Budget Data 1927-46
Box 33-34
Series XXVIII. Willard Straight Items of Interest
Box 34, 36
Series XXIX. Oversize Albums and Memorabilia
Box 35, 37-43
Subseries WSH Publicity Committee Scrapbooks
Box 35, 39-43
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Willard Straight Records
  - Reservations, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - WSH Dining Income, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Daily Food reports, 1957-57 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Open House, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - International Exhibition, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Camp Cayuga, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Parents' Weekend, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - WS banquet, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - All-Straight Party, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Candlelight Room, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Christmas Open House, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Membership, 1952-53 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Membership reports, interviews, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Original Plans, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Anniversary pamphlets, building updates, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Minutes: board and executive committee meeting, 1951-52 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Board of Managers meeting, 1951-52 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Report of the President James N Diefenderfer, 1951-52 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Membership file, 1949-52 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Willard Straight," by Herbert Croly, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Psi U "1900 Club", Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Insurance Records, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Series II. Psi Upsilon Records
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1939-40 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1940-41 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1941-42 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1931-32 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1930-31 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Psi Upsilon records, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Series III. Committee and Building Reports
  - WH 10th anniversary, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Remarks at 10th anniversary, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Remarks by Foster M Coffin
  - WSH Birthday, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Reports on Foreign Students, 1945-51 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Program reports, 1952-53 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Board Function Reports, 1952-53 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Research function board report, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Compiled by Charles Juran
  - Misc Board function reports, 1949-57 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Public relations board function, 1949-50 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Board function reports, 1949-50 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Board function reports, 1948-49 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Reports of coordinators of co-chairmen, 1948-53 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - President's Reports, 1946-51 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Browsing Library Committee, 1938-49 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Committee no longer exists
  - Veterans Committee, 1945-47 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Veterans wives committee, 1946-48 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Women's activities committee, 1949-52 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Servicemen's committee, 1945-46 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Men's and Women's Committee, 1947-48 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Wives Committee, 1945-51 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Women's Tea and Tea committee, 1946-49 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Student Wives Committee, 1950-52 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Forum committee, 1945-48 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hostess Committee Reports, 1945-49 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Frosh House Committee Reports, 1945-53 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Men's House (Men's Activities) Committee Reports, 1946-53 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Publicity Committee Reports, 1946-53 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Poster Committee Reports, 1945-53 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Social Committee Reports, 1945-52 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Music Committee Reports, 1945-53 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Report of the Social Director Summer Session, 1946-47 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
  - General Information Summer Session, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Report of Social Director, Summer, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Social Director Report, Summer, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Summer Session, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Summer Session, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Summer Session, 1936-39 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Board of Managers, 1940-46 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Art, 1944-46 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Employment, Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Radio, 1940-46 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Music, 1942-46 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Shingles left over, 1941-42 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - War Effort, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Board of Managers, 1942-43 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Activities, 1942-43 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    Lists of committee members
  - Board of Managers, 1943-44 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Committee reports, 1943-44 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Board members and managers reports, 1943-44 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Committee reports, 1944-45 (Box 4, Folder 8-12)
  - Former employees and personnel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Statements, 1953-54 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Report of the program director Mary Moore, 1954-55 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Comparative yearly budgets of WSH, 1952-53 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Committee and special project reports, 1953-54 (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
  - Grad. faculty (later grad. activities) Committee., repeats, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Art Committee Reports, 1946-53 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Special Events - Discussion Campus Relations Committee., 1949-51 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report of the Social Director, 1946-47 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Social Director's Report, 1945-46 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Social Director's Annual Report, 1944-45 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report of Social Director, 1943-44 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Social Director's Report, 1942-43 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Report of the Social Director, 1941-42 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Social Director's Report, 1940-41 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Forms file, Volume 1, 1955-56 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Forms file, Volume 2, 1955-56 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Forms file, Volume 1, 1954-55 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Forms file, Volume 2, 1954-55 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - WSH Correspondence, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Activities Committee, 1937-38 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - WSH Activities, 1938-39 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Art, misc., 1938-39 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Activities/Reservations, 1938-39 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Game Room, 1947-48 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Room Reservations, 1957-58 (Box 5, Folder 19-22)
  - Renovations, 1948-50 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Correspondence, 1947-50 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Meetings, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 7-9)
  - Dining Room, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 11-13)
  - Act. Committee, 1938-39 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Art Exhibits, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 15-16)
- Series IV. Payroll Reports
  - Payroll Administration, 1925-26 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Payroll House, 1925-26 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Payroll House, 1926-27 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Payroll House Department, 1927-28 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Payroll Administration, 1927-28 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Payroll House Department, 1927-28 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Payroll House, 1928-29 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Payroll, 1928-29 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Series V. Drama, Theatre, and WSH
  - Willard Straight Hall Organization and Policy, 1925-26 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Willard Straight Hall Misc., 1925-26 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - University Theatre, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - University Theatre, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - University Theatre, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Motion Pictures, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Dramatic Club, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Dramatic Club, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Dramatic Club, 1930 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Dramatic Club, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Dramatic Club, 1932 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Dramatic Club, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Dramatic Club, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Dramatic Club, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Dramatic Club, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Dramatic Club, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Dramatic Club, 1939-40 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Dramatic Club, 1940-41 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- Series VI. Board of Governors Meeting Reports
  - Board of Governors, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Board of Governors, 1926-27 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Board of Governors, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Board of Governors, 1928-29 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Board of Governors, 1929-30 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Board of Governors, 1930-31 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Board of Governors, 1931-32 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Board of Governors, 1932-33 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Board of Governors, 1933-34 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Board of Governors, 1934-35 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Board of Governors, 1935-36 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Board of Governors, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Board of Governors, 1936-37 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Board of Governors, 1937-38 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Board of Governors, 1938-39 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Board of Governors, 1939-40 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Board of Governors, 1941-42 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Board of Governors, 1941-46 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Series VII. House Administration
  - House Payroll, 1944-46 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - House Department, 1929-30 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Administration, 1929-30 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Administration, 1930-31 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - House Department, 1930-31 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Administration, 1931-32 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - House Department, 1931-32 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Administration, 1932-33 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - House Department, 1932-33 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Administration, 1933-34 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - House Department, 1933-34 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Administration, 1934-35 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - House Department, 1934-35 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Administration, 1935-36 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - House Department, 1935-36 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Administration, 1936-37 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - House Department, 1936-37 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Administration, 1937-38 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - House Department, 1937-38 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Administration, 1938-39 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - House Department, 1938-39 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - House Department, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Administration, 1939-41 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Administration, 1945-46 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Series VIII. Willard Straight Hall Activities
  - July, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - August, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - September, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - October, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - November, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - December, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - January, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - March, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - April, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - May, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - June, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - July, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - August, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - September, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - October, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - November, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - December, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - January, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - February, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - March, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - April, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Series IX. Alphabetical Subject Files 1925-27
  - Activities Committee, 1926-27 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Activities Room Memos, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Association University and College Unions Minutes, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Board of Managers, 1926-27 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Board of Managers meeting minutes, 1926-27 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Convention of Association of University and College Unions, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 22-23)
  - University Unions Correspondence, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Sun Correspondence, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Criticisms, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - C.U.C.A., 1926 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Delano and Aldrich, Waterbury HS, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Dramatic Club, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Edward S Drake, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 30-31)
  - Miss Ellison Memos, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Empire State Forest Products Association, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Form Letters, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Horace Moran, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Insurance, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Membership Fees M-Z, 1926-27 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Memos to the desk, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Memos- Mr. Ashbury, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Memos- Mr. Coffin, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Michigan State College, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Musicales, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Musicales, 1926-27 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Miss Peabody, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Princeton, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Publicity Correspondence, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Request for Membership, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Requisitions, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Summer Vacation, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Sunday evening hours, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sunday evening hours, 1926-27 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Supplies A-L, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Supplies M-Z, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Billiard Room, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Employment Correspondence, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Inventory, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - University Unions Data, 1924-27 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, 1925-27 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Series X. Alphabetical Subject Files 1927
  - Alumni Correspondence, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Activities Committee, 1927-28 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Billiard Room, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Class of '01, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Coffin, F.M. Personal, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Coffee House Committee, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Sun Correspondence, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Daily Sun Copy, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Cornellian Council, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - C.U.C.A, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Dance Festival, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Delano and Aldrich- Waterbury, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Dances- Willard Straight, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Dramatic Club, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Mrs. Elmhirst, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Fuertes Paintings, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - General Correspondence N, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - General Correspondence O, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - General Correspondence P, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - General Correspondence R, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - General Correspondence S, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - General Correspondence T, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - General Correspondence U, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - General Correspondence V, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - General Correspondence W, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - General Correspondence XYZ, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Mrs. Grace, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Hart House, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Horace Moran, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Library A-L, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Library M-Z, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Membership Summer Session, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Memos- Mr. Ashbury, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Memos, Miscellaneous, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Memos, Miscellaneous, 1927-28 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Memos, Mr. Coffin, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Memos, Mrs. Grace, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Michigan State College, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Penn State, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Pennsylvania, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Princeton, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Refusals- Reservations, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - WSH Suggestions, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Supplies, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Sunday Evening Hour, 1927-28 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - University Unions Correspondence, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Vault, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Women's Glee Club, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Series XI. Alphabetical Subject Files 1928
  - Activities Committee, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Board of Managers, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Boy Scouts, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - F.M. Coffin Personal, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Cornell Sun, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - C.U.C.A., 1928 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Convention- Association of College and Univ. Unions, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Delano and Aldrich, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Drake, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Employment, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hostess, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Inventory Stock List, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - League of Nations held, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Library, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Library Magazine Subscriptions, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Membership A-L, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Membership M-Z, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - University Unions Data, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Summer Session Membership, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Memberships, 1928-29 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Horace Moran, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Musicales, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Rotary Club, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Supplies, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Sunday Evening House, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Travel Bureau, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - University Unions, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence A to S, 1928-29 (Box 8, Folder 22-39)
    Omitting Q
- Series XII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1929
  - Supplies A-L, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Supplies M-Z, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Act. Com., 1929-30 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence Summer Session, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Teams, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Board of Managers, 1929-30 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - CUCA, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - F.M. Coffin Personal, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Sun, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Boy Scouts, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Billiard Room, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Delano and Aldrich, 1929-30 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Employment, 1929-30 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Membership, 1929-30 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Memos, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Musicales, 1929-30 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Library, 1928-29 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Hostess, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Payments, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence T to XYZ, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 20-23)
    Omitting V
- Series XIII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1930
  - General Correspondence A, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Party Planning, 1930-31 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Straight news, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence B, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Board of Managers, 1930-31 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Billiards Room, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Boy Scouts, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Foster M Coffin Personal, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - C.U.R.W., 1930 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Columbia Univ, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Delano and Aldrich, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Dartmouth, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - E.S Drake, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Employment, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence C to XYZ, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 9-33)
  - Library, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Hostess, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Memos, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Musicales, 1930-31 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Membership, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Membership Summer Session, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Insurance, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Ashbury Resignation, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Food, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - University Unions, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Special Report: Dining Halls, Cornell University, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Supplies A-Z, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Activities Committee, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Series XIV. Alphabetical Subject Files 1931
  - Billiard Room, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Board of Managers, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scouts, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Building and Grounds, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - FMC Personal, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - CUCA, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Columbia, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Delano and Aldrich, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Dartmouth, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Edward S Drake, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Employment, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Hostess, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Hotel, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Insurance, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Library, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence A-XYZ, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 20-43)
  - Membership A-L, 1931-32 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Membership M-Z, 1931-32 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Memos, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Musicales, 1931-32 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Penn State, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Princeton, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Psi Upsilon, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Straight news, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Supplies A-L, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Supplies M-Z, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - University Unions, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Whiting personal, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Yale 2, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Series XV. Alphabetical Subject Files 1932